opjp
This world is corrupt.
The Eve of D-Day - Penguin Force's Hideout - Inside a certain condo - It all started here. There were many similar doors. It's hard to tell which one's real, which one's righteous.
It's all about winning and losing.
Who is ranked above and below you.
The profitable and unprofitable.
The accepted and unaccepted.
この世界は間違えてる
The chosen and unchosen.
勝ったとか　負けたとか
They never try to give...
だれの方が上だとか下だとか
儲かるとか儲からないとか
All they care about is taking!
認められたとか認めてくれないとか
What a miserable world we live in.
選ばれたとか選ばれなかったとか
A world ruled by those who will never amount to anything.
やつらは人に何かを与えようとはせず　いつも求められることばかり考えている
This is already a Frozen World.
この世界はそんなつまらない　きっと何者にもなれないやつらが支配している
But fortunately for us, the Flame of Hope is still burning strong.
The holy flame.
もうここは 氷の世界なんだ
Tomorrow, we will cleanse the world with that flame.
しかし 幸いなるかな
我々の手には希望の松明が燃えている
The 36th Antarctic
Environmental Defense Team
Now's the time to take back...
The beautiful world where the mankind only need true things to survive!
これは聖なる炎
明日 我々は この炎によって 世界を浄化する
This is our Survival Strategy!
今こそ取り戻そう
本当の事だけで 人が生きられる美しい世界を
これが我々の生存戦略なのだ
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
majiwaranai imaginary
The Imaginary and the Real can never mingle
少年少女輪になって
kaiten mokuba chuu wo matte
The merry-go-round twirls into the air
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
tatakai no maku wo kitte otosu
As the curtain of war is torn open
交わらないイマジナリー
himegoto akasu holy night
The Holy Night for divulging secrets
回転木馬宙を舞って
mayonaka hiraku mado temaneku nazo no koe
My window opens at night and a mysterious voice beckons
戦いの幕を切って落とす
秘め事明かすホーリーナイト
真夜中開く窓
shinku no curtain wo hirugaeshite hohoemi kakusu
A crimson curtain conceals the smile
手招く謎の声
深紅のカーテンを翻して
shounen yo ware ni kaere
Boys, come back to me
tokkyuu ressha nocchate
I ended up getting on the midnight express
微笑み隠す
neverland ni tsuretette
Take me away to Neverland
issai gassai ubatte yo
Steal away everything I have
少年よ我に帰れ
特急列車乗っちゃって
ushiro yubi sasaretatte
I don't care if you talk behind my back
ネバーランドに連れてって
ichimokusan ni nigechatte iiyo
I'll just run away at full speed
一切合切奪ってよ
zenbu oki ni mesu mama
Do as you please
後ろ指さされたって
一目散に逃げちゃっていいよ
全部お気に召すまま
shounen shoujo wa ni natte
The boys and girls form a ring
nobashita te wa kuu wo kitte ochiru
Extended hands cut down through the air
mawari hajimeru destiny
Destiny begins to turn
少年少女輪になって
伸ばした手は空を切って落ちる
回り始めるディステニー
バカな人達
Fools.
This pretend family of yours can't last forever.
そんな嘘の家族ごっこがいつまでも続くわけがない
僕達はホントの家族だ
We are a real family!
そう思ってるのは貴方だけかもしれなくてよ
You're probably the only one who believes that.
We are family...!
家族だ　僕達は
私は絶対認めないわ
I will never accept it.
晶ちゃん
Sho...
ひまり
Himari!
Are you all right?
大丈夫　怪我はない
Are you hurt?
思い出したよ
I remember now.
晶ちゃんが　私の
Sho is my...
運命の人
Soulmate.
Let's eat!
頂きます
どう
What do you think?
うまい
It's good!
Yeah, it's delicious!
うん　美味しいよ
ホント　よかった
Really?
I'm so glad.
ひまり　料理の腕上げたな
You've gotten better at cooking!
うん　入院中ずっとイメージトレーニングで練習してたんだ
Yup!
I've been doing visualization training the whole time in hospital!
イメトレで上達するの
You can actually improve just by imagination?
なんだ　お前よりうまいからって僻むなよ
What, are you bitter because she's better than you?
別に　僻んでる
I'm not bitter or anything...
それより　このうまい浅漬け食べてみろよ
Anyway, try these tasty pickles!
I made them myself!
俺が作ったんだ
All you did was put stuff in a bag and squeeze.
って　袋に入れて揉むだけじゃん
The key is how I squeeze them.
揉み方にコツがあんだよ　俺の揉み方にな
The way I squeeze.
朝からいやらしい手つきするな
Don't be making that dirty look so early in the morning!
何がだよ　どこがだよ
What's dirty about it? Tell me.
美味しい　晶ちゃんのお味噌汁は御母さんと同じ味がするね
It's delicious.
Sho's miso soup tastes just like Mom's.
Stop it.
やめろよ
高倉家の家族は僕達だけだ
We're the only members of the Takakura family.
そうだな
You're right.
To'oh General Hospital
How electrifying.
痺れるね
I'll tell you a story of love today.
さて　今日はある恋のお話です
If you chase, it'll run. If you run, you'll be chased.
追えば逃げ　逃げると追われる
Things were going so well, but things end. Just like that.
あれほどうまくいっていたのに　ある日突然そっけない
It ran away!
逃げられた
What would you do?
さあ　君ならどうする
私だったら　追い掛けない
If it were me, I wouldn't chase.
Why not?
なぜ
I'd get tired.
疲れちゃうし
うーん　確かに　そういうタイプの人もいるね
True.
Some people think that way.
So, you're declaring that you'll only be on the running side.
つまり 君は逃げる役目しかやらないと宣言するわけだ
What do you mean?
うーん　どういう意味
If both sides are running,
両方が逃げるんだから
No way!
それはお互いが私からは近づきませんよと相手に言うのと同じって事さ（まあ　そんな）
that's same as telling each other "I won't come near you."
つまり
So?
No!
いや　聞きたくない
I don't want to hear it!
その恋は実らない
Your love won't come to fruition.
I'm fine with that.
それでいいよ　私 恋なんかしないもん
I won't fall in love.
Oh?
そう
I'm just curious...
たとえばだけど
うん
相手が逃げたら　私は追えばいいの
If the other side is running,
should I just chase?
Will that bring love to fruition?
それで 恋は実るの
Sometimes it will.
実る場合もある
そうかな
Are you sure?
Wouldn't the other side keep running,
そういう相手は逃げ続けて
and refuse to give me the fruit?
絶対こっちには実りの果実を与えないんじゃないかな
That's a sharp observation.
鋭いね
そう　逃げる者は追う者に決して果実を与えない
You're right.
The chased will never give the fruit to the chaser.
それをすると　楽ちんなゲームが終わるからね （終わりたい 終わりたくない ）
If they did, the simple game will end.
I want it to end!
I don't want it to end!
That's mean.
酷い
君は果実を手に入れたいわけだ
So, you want to obtain the fruit.
Kiss alone is not enough?
キスをするだけじゃ　ダメなんだね
キスは無限じゃないんだよ
Kisses are perishable.
They'll be consumed.
消費されちゃうんだよ
果実がないのにキスばかりしていると
If I kept kissing without the fruit, I'll end up empty.
Hot Air
Testimony
Accident
Cold Current
Hot Air
Testimony
私は空っぽになっちゃうよ
空っぽになったら ダメなのかい
What's wrong with being empty?
空っぽになったら ポイされるんだよ
If you become empty, you'll be thrown away.
ポイされてもいいじゃないか
Who cares if you get thrown away?
百回のキスをやりかえすんだよ
You can kiss a hundred times over.
無理だよ
I can't.
そうなっちゃったら心が凍りついて 息も出来なくなっちゃう
If I did, my heart would freeze over and I wouldn't be able to breathe.
Then, kiss over and over until just before your heart freezes over and you suffocate.
じゃあ心が凍りついて息も出来なくなるギリギリまでキスを繰り返せばいい
That's just too pathetic.
そんなの惨めだよ
惨めでもいいじゃないか　キスができるんだから
Who cares if you're pathetic? You'll get to kiss.
何もしないで　凍りついても面白くないよ
Where's the fun if you freeze over without doing anything?
If that's the case, wouldn't it be more fun if you freeze over from kisses?
だったらキスをして凍りつく方が楽しいんじゃないかな
どうすれば
What should I do?
Let your heart decide.
気持ちに任せろって事
キスだけが果実じゃないのかな
Maybe kisses are the only real fruits.
Flammable, non-flammable.
燃える　燃えない
Flammable.
燃えると　こっちは燃えないか
This one's non-flammable.
Ahh! What a pain in the ass!
なー　面倒くせぇ
罰当番なんて　小学生じゃあるまいし
We're getting punished? What are we, elementary schoolers?
It had nothing to do with us, right?
俺達関係ないじゃん　なー
たまたま同じ所にいたからって
We just happened to be in the same place.
連帯責任って何
Why are we held responsible too?
ったく　あいつらのせいだ
Damn it. It's all their fault.
腐った蜜柑だよ　一緒にいるとこっちまでカビ出くる
Those bad apples!
One rotten apple spoils the bunch!
ONE Man's
Trash is
ANOTHER
Man's
Treasure
罰は僕が受けるべきだったんだ
I should've been the one to be punished.
高倉家が罰を受けなきゃならないとしても
If the Takakura family must be punished,
it should've been directed only at me.
それは僕だけが受けるべき罰なんだ
どういうこと
What do you mean?
I will never forgive my parents.
父さんと母さんのこと 僕は絶対許さないよ
Those two took so many lives... even your sister's.
あの二人は　多くの人の命を
君のお姉さんまで
That's... not your sin.
それは 晶馬君の罪じゃないよ
The sins of the Takakura family are mine.
高倉家の罪は僕の罪
Mine alone!
僕だけの罪なんだ
晶馬君だけの罪
Your's alone?
だって
After all, Himari...
ひまりは
Himari was... chosen by me as family.
ひまりは 僕が家族に選んだんだ
Shoma - 10 Years Ago - Kiga Group's hideout - This is where we met. I was alone back then. That's why I found her.
A part of this city was cleansed by our holy fire on that day.
あの日　我らの聖なる炎で
この間違えた世界の一部は浄化された
But our goal has yet to be achieved.
だが　我々の志は まだ 果たされていない
Society call us criminals.
世間は我々を犯罪者と呼ぶ
Ever since that day, many of our comrades have had their freedom unjustly taken away.
あの日以来　多くの同志が不当に自由を奪われた
However, the Flame of Hope burning in our hearts cannot be so easily extinguished!
しかし　そんなことで 我々の胸に燃える松明の炎は消せない
The present is bliss.
今は至福の時である
We changed the organization's name to Kiga Group to mislead them.
企鵝の会と名前を改めたのも やつらの目を欺くため
我々は次の聖なる日に向け　しくしくと準備を進めるのだ
We will prepare the next Judgement Day in shadows!
お兄様　何を見てらっしゃるの
What are you looking at, brother?
Why isn't that boy listening to the speech?
あの子　どうしてお話を聞かないのかしら
He probably got bored.
飽きたんだろう
The speech is about to get to the important part: about our father.
次はもっと大事な私達のお父様のお話なのに
He should be listening.
あの子も聞くべきだわ
Do you live here?
君　ここに住んでる子
何時から
For how long?
Forever.
ずっと
How long is that?
ずっとって
Don't know.
さあ
一緒に遊ばない
Wanna play together?
I'm waiting for my mom.
ママを待ってるから
Let's share it.
一緒に食べない
いらない
No, thanks.
My mom said not to take things from strangers.
ママが知らない人からもらっちゃ駄目だって
Do you know the story of the first man and woman on Earth?
ね　地上で最初の男と女の話って知ってる
No.
知らない
一緒に運命の果実を食べたんだ
They shared the fruit of fate.
My life will never bear fruit though.
私の人生に果実なんてないから
What are you doing?
何してるの
A cat.
猫
Is it yours?
君の猫
No.
ううん
Why was it left here?
どうしてこんなところに　可愛いのに
It's so cute.
Come.
おいで
Because it's an unneeded child.
いらない子供だから
It was probably cared for at first.
多分 最初は可愛がられたんだよ
But its cuteness was consumed.
でも 可愛いが消費された　だから捨てられたの
So it was thrown away.
Oh, right! I have some milk.
そうだ　ミルクがあるよ
Don't. You can't keep it, right?
やめて　飼えないんでしょ
To be unchosen is to die.
選ばれないことは死ぬことなの
" No Pets Allowed "
Please contact superintendent
if you see one.
It's drinking.
飲んでる
Let's take care of it until it's adopted by someone.
もらってくれる人が見つかるまで　僕達で面倒を見ようよ
Okay.
うん
We have to give it a name.
名前決めなくちゃ
It's so warm.
暖かい　お日様みたい
Like the sun.
What's your name?
君の名前は
Himari. Just like "hidamari," a sunny spot.
ひまり
日だまりのひまり
Oh, that's a nice name.
素敵な名前だね
Let's give it a warm name like yours.
じゃあ　君みたいに暖かい名前は
I guess not.
駄目か
Sunny.
サンちゃん
Sunny...
サンちゃん　英語か
English, huh?
Good idea! Sunny it is!
いいね　そうしようよ
You're Sunny starting today.
今日から　サンちゃんだよ
" NO PETS ALLOWED "
Someone broke the rule recently.
It will not be tolerated!!
Sorry.
御免
It's not your fault.
晶ちゃんのせいじゃないよ
But...
でも
It wasn't chosen.
選ばれなかったのよ　あの子は
This world is divided into the Chosen and the Unchosen.
この世界は選ばれるか選ばれないか
To be unchosen is to die.
選ばれないことは 死ぬこと
I never saw Himari in the condo again after that day.
その日を最後に　ひまりはあのマンションから姿を消した
To Sho
Good bye
（さようなら　しょうちゃん）
Goodbye.
" No Pets Allowed "
Thank  you for your cooperation...
Please continue to obey the rules
and have a fun life!!
さようなら　子供ブロイラーに行きます
I'm going to the Child Broiler.
" No Pets Allowed "
Thank  you for your cooperation...
Please continue to obey the rules
and have a fun life!!
Hey, Dad.
ね　父さん
What's the Child Broiler?
子供ブロイラーって何
The destination of children abandoned by society.
社会から　見捨てられた子供達が　行く場所だ
We can't do anything about it. We can't save them.
我々も手を出すことが出来ないし　救えない
It's a Frozen World.
氷の世界だ
What will happen to children who went there?
そこにいた子供はどうなるの
They become invisible.
透明になる
What do you mean?
どういうこと
They will never amount to anything.
彼らは何者にもなれない
Are you saying they'll die?
死ぬってこと
No way...!
そんな
Many children are turning invisible even as we speak.
この瞬間にも　大勢の子供達が透明にされている
This world is corrupt for allowing it to happen.
それを放置しているこの世界は間違っている
So, we must...
だから　我々は
Shoma?
晶馬
To Sho.
晶ちゃんへ　さようなら
Goodbye.
I'm going to Child Broiler.
子供ブロイラーに行きます
Thank you for everything.
今までありがとう
I was actually really happy when you first talked to me.
初めて声をかけてくれた時　本当はすごくうれしかった
Ever since, I've been waiting for you there.
あれからね　私は晶ちゃんを待つことにしたんだ
My mom never returned, but...
ママは帰って来なかったけど
I got to wait for you, so...
私は晶ちゃんを待つことが出来たから　寂しくなかったよ
I wasn't lonely at all.
That was the first time I'd ever thought waiting wasn't painful.
待つってことは　辛くないことだって初めて思ったんだ
Sho, Sunny, and me.
晶ちゃんとサンちゃんと私
We were like a family and it was fun.
家族みたいで　楽しかった
So I'll take this scarf with me.
だから　このマフラーはもらっていくね
I'll never forget, no matter what.
私　何があっても忘れないよ
I'll treasure our encounter forever.
晶ちゃんと出会ったことは私の宝物なんだ
So I'm not scared of anything anymore.
だから　もう何も怖くないよ
Child Broiler
ひまりちゃん
Himari!
Child Broiler
Administration
Even if I become invisible, no one can take my treasure away.
透明にされても
この宝物は誰にも消せないよ
Like tin soldiers melting into the shape of a heart.
暖炉で燃え残った錫の兵隊の心臓みたいに
So I was happy.
だから　幸せ
Because there is someone...
私が世界にいたことを
who will remember that I existed.
覚えてくれてる人がいるんだもん
Himari!
陽毬ちゃん
I actually knew that story of the first man and woman on Earth.
地上で最初の男と女の話
私　知ってたよ
The two accepted their punishment.
二人は罰を受けたんだ
To live is punishment in itself.
生きるってことは罰なんだね
But even if it is, I wanted to spend my time with Sho.
でも　罰でも　晶ちゃんと一緒にいたかった
So...
だから　選ばれたかった
I wanted to be chosen.
Himari...
ひまりちゃん
Himari!
ひまり
Let's share the fruit of fate.
運命の果実を一緒に食べよう
Thank you for choosing me.
選んでくれて　ありがとう
That's right.
そうだ　僕が選んだ
I was the one who chose her.
I was the one who turned Himari into a Takakura.
僕がひまりを高倉家の子供にしてしまったんだ
Many children are turning invisible even as we speak.
Ogikubo's
flavor
Rina-chan
この瞬間にも　大勢の子供達が透明にされている
We cannot possibly forgive this world for allowing it to happen.
それを放置しているこの世界を許しておいていいはずがない
だからこそ
Thus, we must cleanse this world for the inevitable Judgement Day.
我々は来たるべき聖なる日に世界を浄化しなければならない
You're right.
そうだよ　ひまりにはどうしても治療費が必要なんだ
Himari absolutely needs money for her treatment.
I'm the only one who can save Himari.
ひまりを救えるのは俺しかいない
You're all boiling up nicely.
よい塩梅に煮えておるな
I shall now add these Southern spices into the mix!
では　この南蛮ドライの粉末を入れてくれよ
You'll melt into sludge!
ドロッドロの熱々になる故　その方　覚悟いたせ
Prepare youself!
We're having wholesome Apple Curry tonight!
今宵はリンゴたっぷりカレーじゃ
Come back soon, Kan and Sho.
冠ちゃんも晶ちゃんも早く帰ってくるのだぞ
Thank You For Choosing Me
aishite kurenakya dame sa
You have to love me
愛してくれなきゃ駄目さ
omae no himitsu no kobeya ni iresasete
Let me in to your little secret room
お前の秘密の小部屋に入れさせて
愛してくれなきゃ駄目さ
aishite kurenakya dame sa
You have to love me
omae wa konya kashikiri no Private Girl
Tonight, you're my exclusive Private Girl
お前は今夜貸切のプライベート　ガール
mezamashidokei ga naru made no koi
Our love lasts until the alarm clock goes off
目覚まし時計が鳴るまでの恋
itsumade mo tsuzuku wake wa naidarou
It won't last forever
いつまでも続くわけはないだろう
sukoshi dake kanashii hanashi dane
Don't you think that's a little sad?
少しだけ悲しい話だね
kotoba wa nani mo iranai
We don't need words
言葉は何もいらない
omae no kokoro no nukumori ni furesasete
Let me feel the warmth of your heart
お前の心の温もりに触れさせて
kotoba wa nanimo iranai
We don't need words
言葉は何もいらない
omae no shiroi hada ga mabushisugite
Your milky white skin is just shining so brightly
お前の白い肌が眩しすぎて
me ni mieru mono wa subete onaji
Everything seems the same to me
目に見えるものは全て同じ
tobira no mukau wa Moebius no keshiki dake
The vast scenary of Moebius in the other side of the door
扉の向うはメビウスの景色だけ
NO NO NO
NO, NO, NO
This world is corrupt.
この世界は間違えている
Who made those rules?
ルールを作った奴は誰だ
I will not be ruled by them!
俺はそんなものには支配されない
生存戦略　誰にも消せないよ
Lily Hoshino
Survival Strategy. No one can take them away.